// eslint-disable-next-line no-undef
export default data = [
  {
    question: '1. What is the largest desert in the world by area?',
    options: ['Sahara', 'Atacama', 'Gobi', 'Antarctic desert'],
    optionsLetter: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correct_option: 'Antarctic desert', //fix _ name
  },
  {
    question: '2. What is the driest desert in the world?',
    options: ['Sahara', 'Atacama', 'Gobi', 'Kalahari'],
    optionsLetter: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correct_option: 'Atacama',
  },
  {
    question:
      '3. In which desert is the city of Libya, one of the largest oases in the world, located?',
    options: ['Sahara', 'Atacama', 'Gobi', 'Arctic'],
    optionsLetter: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correct_option: 'Sahara',
  },
  {
    question: '4. Which desert is part of the historic Silk Road?',
    options: ['Sahara', 'Atacama', 'Gobi', 'Kalahari'],
    optionsLetter: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correct_option: 'Gobi',
  },
  {
    question:
      '5. Which desert is located in Australia and is one of the largest deserts in the southern hemisphere?',
    options: [
      'The Great Salt Marsh Basin',
      'Great Sandy Desert',
      'Great Dividing Range',
      'Gobi',
    ],
    optionsLetter: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correct_option: 'Great Sandy Desert',
  },
  {
    question:
      '6. Which desert is located in South America and is known for its diverse flora and fauna, including cacti and camels?',
    options: ['Atacama', 'Patagonia', 'Kalahari', 'Gobi'],
    optionsLetter: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correct_option: 'Atacama',
  },
  //7
  {
    question:
      '7. In which desert is the world`s deepest salt water body located?',
    options: ['Sahara', 'Atacama', 'Gobi', 'The Great Salt Basin'],
    optionsLetter: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correct_option: 'Atacama',
  },
  //8
  {
    question:
      '8. Which desert is known for its unique shape of sand dunes, sometimes reaching heights of more than 200 meters?',
    options: [
      'The Great Salt Marsh Basin',
      'Great Sandy Desert',
      'Sahara',
      'Kalahari',
    ],
    optionsLetter: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correct_option: 'Great Sandy Desert',
  },
  //9
  {
    question:
      '9. Which desert is home to the endangered species of antelope known as the "Saharan antelope" or "Saharan gazelle"?',
    options: ['Gobi', 'Kalahari', 'Sahara', 'Atacama'],
    optionsLetter: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correct_option: 'Sahara',
  },
  //10
  {
    question:
      '10. Which desert south of India is known for its historical heritage and the great forts that have survived from the time of the Rejputans?',
    options: [
      'Suddenly',
      'The Great Salt Basin',
      'Great Sandy Desert',
      'Sahara',
    ],
    optionsLetter: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correct_option: 'Great Sandy Desert',
  },
];
